{
    "id": "35e688d17b384670b569f525dfaaedc2",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The striking workers have decided to ……………………….. the meeting for an indefinite period.",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put down",
                "put off",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a168335029d14c9c9385083c8f47550a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The President ………………………… the leader of the party that won the most seats to form the government.",
            "description": "To call upon is to invite.",
            "answers": [
                "called in",
                "called out",
                "called upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2fadb0ed2a0c4abe896f2fe4b594fc82"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager is faced with more problems than he can easily ………………………..",
            "description": "To get over is to overcome.",
            "answers": [
                "get over",
                "get across",
                "get out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c8141a0e61484e2a820ad1d4800eb313"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor advised the patient to …………………………….. smoking.",
            "description": "To give up is to stop.",
            "answers": [
                "give up",
                "give in",
                "give out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ec8b307f9294acaaf81360fbf2c2458"
        },
        {
            "question": "The travelers …………………………. very early in the morning.",
            "description": "To get up is to rise from bed.",
            "answers": [
                "got out",
                "got up",
                "got in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f6d7c7d091e4b2ea260c3217b8a3801"
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient had ………………………….. before the doctor arrived.",
            "description": "To pass away is to die. ",
            "answers": [
                "passed out",
                "passed off",
                "passed away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fbb8721a9df546db945c138bf3d0e21a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He faced his enemy bravely but in the end he had to ……………………….",
            "description": "To give in is to surrender.",
            "answers": [
                "give out",
                "give in",
                "give off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce48af4bff1740e892d742f44e8965f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The job will …………………………… very little of your time.",
            "description": "To take up is to consume or occupy.",
            "answers": [
                "take out",
                "take in",
                "take up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b44973ad8a34dfb8e9cedabb45f0335"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ………………………… the files carefully.",
            "description": "To go through is to examine.",
            "answers": [
                "go through",
                "go after",
                "get through"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "429d50686f644f04baa2ee29d5c0a8b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The firemen worked hard for hours to ……………………….. the fire in the factory.",
            "description": "To put out is to extinguish.",
            "answers": [
                "put off",
                "put out",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16b2d7f9fa6e40968c4ede08f210f083"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was his carelessness that ……………………………. the accident.",
            "description": "To bring something about is to cause it to happen.",
            "answers": [
                "brought about",
                "brought out",
                "brought up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e726a9ba858f4e4e9f099faa52c3f746"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came over",
                "came out",
                "came across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "442405d4188c4772906e4f80aaf61785"
        }
    ]
}